and how everything manages to come back into style. And a few more beers, I said, "There has to be some stuff that hasn't come back." (Laughter) Then one more beer and it was, whatever happened to the mustache? Why hasn't that made a comeback? (Laughter) So then there was a lot more beers, and then the day ended with a challenge to bring the mustache back. (Laughter) So in Australia, "mo" is slang for mustache, so we renamed the month of November "Movember" and created some pretty basic rules, which still stand today. And they are: start the month clean-shaven, rock a mustache -- not a beard, not a goatee, a mustache -- for the 30 days of November, and then we agreed that we would come together at the end of the month, have a mustache-themed party, and award a prize for the best, and of course, the worst mustache. (Laughter) Now trust me, when you're growing a mustache back in 2003, and there were 30 of us back then, and this was before the ironic hipster mustache movement — (Laughter) — it created a lot of controversy. (Laughter) So my boss wouldn't let me go and see clients. My girlfriend at the time, who's no longer my girlfriend — (Laughter) — hated it. Parents would shuffle kids away from us. (Laughter) But we came together at the end of the month and we celebrated our journey, and it was a real journey. And we had a lot of fun, and in 2004, I said to the guys, "That was so much fun. We need to legitimize this so we can get away with it year on year." (Laughter) So we started thinking about that, and we were inspired by the women around us and all they were doing for breast cancer. And we thought, you know what, there's nothing for men's health. Why is that? Why can't we combine growing a mustache and doing something for men's health? And I started to research that topic, and discovered prostate cancer is the male equivalent of breast cancer in terms of the number of men that die from it and are diagnosed with it. But there was nothing for this cause, so we married growing a mustache with prostate cancer, and then we created our tagline, which is, "Changing the face of men's health." And that eloquently describes the challenge, changing your appearance for the 30 days, and also the outcome that we're trying to achieve: getting men engaged in their health, having them have a better understanding about the health risks that they face. So with that model, I then cold-called the CEO of the Prostate Cancer Foundation. I said to him, "I've got the most amazing idea that's going to transform your organization." (Laughter) And I didn't want to share with him the idea over the phone, so I convinced him to meet with me for coffee in Melbourne in 2004. And we sat down, and I shared with him my vision of getting men growing mustaches across Australia, raising awareness for this cause, and funds for his organization. And I needed a partnership to legitimately do that. And I said, "We're going to come together at the end, we're going to have a mustache-themed party, we're going to have DJs, we're going to celebrate life, and we're going to change the face of men's health." And he just looked at me and laughed, and he said, he said, "Adam, that's a really novel idea, but we're an ultraconservative organization. We can't have anything to do with you." (Laughter) So I paid for coffee that day — (Laughter) — and his parting comment as we shook hands was, "Listen, if you happen to raise any money out of this, we'll gladly take it." (Laughter) So my lesson that year was persistence. And we persisted, and we got 450 guys growing mustaches, and together we raised 54,000 dollars, and we donated every cent of that to the Prostate Cancer Foundation of Australia, and that represented at the time the single biggest donation they'd ever received. So from that day forward, my life has become about a mustache. Every day -- this morning, I wake up and go, my life is about a mustache. (Laughter) Essentially, I'm a mustache farmer. (Laughter) And my season is November. (Applause) (Applause) So in 2005, the campaign got more momentum, was more successful in Australia and then New Zealand, and then in 2006 we came to a pivotal point. It was consuming so much of our time after hours on weekends that we thought, we either need to close this down or figure a way to fund Movember so that I could quit my job and go and spend more time in the organization and take it to the next level. It's really interesting when you try and figure a way to fund a fundraising organization built off growing mustaches. (Laughter) Let me tell you that there's not too many people interested in investing in that, not even the Prostate Cancer Foundation, who we'd raised about 1.2 million dollars for at that stage. So again we persisted, and Foster's Brewing came to the party and gave us our first ever sponsorship, and that was enough for me to quit my job, I did consulting on the side. And leading into Movember 2006, we'd run through all the money from Foster's, we'd run through all the money I had, and essentially we had no money left, and we'd convinced all our suppliers -- creative agencies, web development agencies, hosting companies, whatnot -- to delay their billing until December. So we'd racked up at this stage about 600,000 dollars worth of debt. So if Movember 2006 didn't happen, the four founders, well, we would've been broke, we would've been homeless, sitting on the street with mustaches. (Laughter) But we thought, you know what, if that's the worst thing that happens, so what? We're going to have a lot of fun doing it, and it taught us the importance of taking risks and really smart risks. Then in early 2007, a really interesting thing happened. We had Mo Bros from Canada, from the U.S., and from the U.K. emailing us and calling us and saying, hey, there's nothing for prostate cancer. Bring this campaign to these countries. So we thought, why not? Let's do it. So I cold-called the CEO of Prostate Cancer Canada, and I said to him, "I have this most amazing concept." (Laughter) "It's going to transform your organization. I don't want to tell you about it now, but will you meet with me if I fly all the way to Toronto?" So I flew here, met down on Front Street East, and we sat in the boardroom, and I said, "Right, here's my vision of getting men growing mustaches all across Canada raising awareness and funds for your organization." And he looked at me and laughed and said, "Adam, sounds like a really novel idea, but we're an ultraconservative organization." (Laughter) I've heard this before. I know how it goes. But he said, "We will partner with you, but we're not going to invest in it. You need to figure a way to bring this campaign across here and make it work." So what we did was, we took some of the money that we raised in Australia to bring the campaign across to this country, the U.S, and the U.K., and we did that because we knew, if this was successful, we could raise infinitely more money globally than we could just in Australia. And that money fuels research, and that research will get us to a cure. And we're not about finding an Australian cure or a Canadian cure, we're about finding the cure. So in 2007, we brought the campaign across here, and it was, it set the stage for the campaign. It wasn't as successful as we thought it would be. We were sort of very gung ho with our success in Australia and New Zealand at that stage. So that year really taught us the importance of being patient and really understanding the local market before you become so bold as to set lofty targets. But what I'm really pleased to say is, in 2010, Movember became a truly global movement. Canada was just pipped to the post in terms of the number one fundraising campaign in the world. Last year we had 450,000 Mo Bros spread across the world and together we raised 77 million dollars. (Applause) And that makes Movember now the biggest funder of prostate cancer research and support programs in the world. And that is an amazing achievement when you think about us growing mustaches. (Laughter) And for us, we have redefined charity. Our ribbon is a hairy ribbon. (Laughter) Our ambassadors are the Mo Bros and the Mo Sistas, and I think that's been fundamental to our success. We hand across our brand and our campaign to those people. We let them embrace it and interpret it in their own way. So now I live in Los Angeles, because the Prostate Cancer Foundation of the U.S. is based there, and I always get asked by the media down there, because it's so celebrity-driven, "Who are your celebrity ambassadors?" And I say to them, "Last year we were fortunate enough to have 450,000 celebrity ambassadors." And they go, "What, what do you mean?" And it's like, everything single person, every single Mo Bro and Mo Sista that participates in Movember is our celebrity ambassador, and that is so, so important and fundamental to our success. Now what I want to share with you is one of my most touching Movember moments, and it happened here in Toronto last year, at the end of the campaign. I was out with a team. It was the end of Movember. We'd had a great campaign, and to be honest, we'd had our fair share of beer that night, but I said, "You know what, I think we've got one more bar left in us." (Laughter) So we piled into a taxi, and this is our taxi driver, and I was sitting in the back seat, and he turned around and said, "Where are you going?" And I said, "Hang on, that is an amazing mustache." (Laughter) And he said, "I'm doing it for Movember." And I said, "So am I." And I said, "Tell me your Movember story." And he goes, "Listen, I know it's about men's health, I know it's about prostate cancer, but this is for breast cancer." And I said, "Okay, that's interesting." And he goes, "Last year, my mom passed away from breast cancer in Sri Lanka, because we couldn't afford proper treatment for her," and he said, "This mustache is my tribute to my mom." And we sort of all choked up in the back of the taxi, and I didn't tell him who I was, because I didn't think it was appropriate, and I just shook his hand and I said, "Thank you so much. Your mom would be so proud." And from that moment I realized that Movember is so much more than a mustache, having a joke. It's about each person coming to this platform, embracing it in their own way, and being significant in their own life. For us now at Movember, we really focus on three program areas, and having a true impact: awareness and education,
y de cómo todas las modas regresan. Unas cuantas cervezas más, dije, "tiene que haber alguna cosa que no haya vuelto". (Risas) Luego de una cerveza más, ¿qué pasó con el bigote? ¿Por qué no ha regresado? (Risas) Entonces hubo muchas más cervezas y el día terminó con el reto para traer de vuelta el bigote. (Risas) En Australia, "mo" es jerga para bigote, así que cambiamos el nombre del mes de noviembre, "Movember", y formulamos algunas reglas muy básicas, que siguen en pie hoy en día. Son: iniciar el mes bien afeitado, dejarse un bigote —no una barba, no una chivera, un bigote— durante los 30 días de noviembre y, a continuación, convenimos que nos reuniríamos al final del mes, a celebrar una fiesta temática de bigote, con un premio para el mejor y, por supuesto, el peor bigote. (Risas) Créanme, cuando nos dejábamos el bigote, allá en 2003, y éramos 30 entonces, y antes del movimiento del irónico bigote 'hipster' —(Risas)— se generó mucha controversia. (Risas) Mi jefe no me dejaba ir a ver clientes. Mi novia del momento, que ya no es mi novia —(Risas) — lo odiaba. Los padres alejaban sus hijos de nosotros. (Risas) Pero llegamos juntos al final del mes y celebramos nuestra aventura, y fue una aventura real. Nos divertimos mucho, y en 2004, les dije a los chicos: "Eso fue muy divertido. Necesitamos legitimarlo para que podamos llegar lejos con él en un año". (Risas) Así que empezamos a pensar en ello y fuimos inspirados por las mujeres alrededor nuestro y todo lo que hacían para el cáncer de mama. Y pensamos, sabes qué, no hay nada para la salud de los hombres. ¿Por qué? ¿Por qué no podemos combinar el crecimiento de un bigote con hacer algo para la salud de los hombres? Y comencé a investigar el tema y descubrí que el cáncer de próstata es el equivalente masculino del cáncer de mama en cuanto al número de hombres que mueren de esto y que se les diagnostica uno. Pero no había nada por esta causa, así que casamos el dejarse crecer el bigote con el cáncer de próstata, y, a continuación, creamos nuestro lema, que es: "Cambiar la cara de la salud de los hombres", que describe con elocuencia el desafío, cambiar su apariencia por 30 días, y también el resultado que estamos tratando de lograr: hombres comprometidos con su salud, que tienen una mejor comprensión de los riesgos de salud que enfrentan. Así que con ese modelo llamé en frío al director de la Fundación de Cáncer de Próstata. Le dije: "tengo la idea más maravillosa que va a transformar su organización". (Risas) Y como no quería compartirla por teléfono, lo convencí de reunirse conmigo para tomar café en Melbourne en 2004. Nos sentamos y compartí con él mi visión de conseguir hombres que se dejaran el bigote por toda Australia, logrando sensibilizar por esta causa y fondos para su organización. Y necesitaba una asociación para hacerlo legítimamente. Y dije: "vamos a llegar juntos hasta el final, vamos a tener una fiesta temática de bigote, vamos a tener DJs, vamos a celebrar la vida y vamos a cambiar la cara de la salud de los hombres". Él solo me miró, se rió y me dijo: "Adam, es una idea realmente novedosa, pero somos una organización ultraconservadora. No podemos tener nada que ver con Uds.". (Risas) Así que pagué el café ese día —(Risas)— y su comentario de despedida cuando nos estrechamos las manos fue: "Escucha, si llegas a conseguir algún dinero, con mucho gusto lo aceptaremos". (Risas) Así que mi lección ese año fue persistencia. Y persistimos, y conseguimos 450 hombres dejándose el bigote, y juntos recaudamos 54 000 dólares, y donamos cada centavo a la Fundación de Cáncer de Próstata de Australia, lo que representó en su momento la donación más grande de todos los tiempos. Así que desde ese día, mi vida ha girado alrededor del bigote. Cada día... esta mañana, me levanté y seguí, mi vida es sobre un bigote. (Risas) Esencialmente, soy un agricultor de bigotes. (Risas) Y mi temporada es en noviembre. (Aplausos) (Aplausos) Así que en 2005, la campaña recibió más impulso, tuvo más éxito en Australia y luego en Nueva Zelanda, y, después, en el 2006 llegamos a un punto crítico. Esto consumía tanto tiempo de nuestras horas libres los fines de semana que pensamos que teníamos o bien que cerrarlo o lograr una manera de financiar Movember para que yo pudiera dejar mi trabajo y pasar más tiempo en la organización y llevarla al siguiente nivel. Es realmente interesante cuando uno intenta e imagina una forma de financiar una organización de recaudación de fondos construida sobre los bigotes. (Risas) Déjenme decirles que no hay demasiada gente interesada en invertir en eso, ni siquiera la Fundación de Cáncer de Próstata, a la que le habíamos conseguido alrededor de 1,2 millones de dólares en ese momento. Así que de nuevo persistimos, y Foster's Brewing se unió a la fiesta y nos dio nuestro primer patrocinio, que fue suficiente para dejar mi trabajo, hice consultoría en paralelo. Esto nos lleva a Movember 2006, gastamos todo el dinero de Foster's, gastamos todo el dinero que tenía, y básicamente no había quedado nada, y convencimos a todos nuestros proveedores —agencias creativas, desarrolladoras de web, compañías de hospedaje y demás— de retrasar sus facturas hasta diciembre. Así que habíamos acumulado para entonces cerca de 600 000 dólares en deuda. Por lo que Movember 2006 no se dio, los cuatro fundadores, bueno, hubiéramos quebrado, hubiéramos estado en la calle, sentados en la acera con bigotes. (Risas) Pero pensamos, sabes qué, si esto es lo peor que sucede, ¿qué pasa? Vamos a divertirnos un montón haciéndolo, y esto nos enseñó la importancia de asumir riesgos y riesgos realmente inteligentes. Luego, a principios de 2007, sucedió algo muy interesante. Tuvimos Mo Bros de Canadá, de los EE.UU. y del Reino Unido, que nos enviaron correos y nos llamaron diciendo: ¡Hola!, no hay nada para el cáncer de próstata. Traigan esa campaña a estos países. Así que pensamos, ¿por qué no? Vamos a hacerlo. Así que llamé en frío al director de Cáncer de Próstata Canadá y le dije: "tengo el concepto más increíble". (Risas) "Va a transformar su organización. No quiero hablarle de ello ahora, pero ¿podría reunirse conmigo si vuelo a Toronto?" Así que volé aquí, nos reunimos en Front Street East, y nos sentamos en la sala de juntas, y dije: "bien, esta es mi visión, conseguir hombres que se dejen crecer bigotes por todo Canadá, generar sensibilización y recaudar fondos para su organización". Me miró, se rió y dijo: "Adam, suena como una idea realmente novedosa, pero somos una organización ultraconservadora". (Risas) He escuchado esto antes. Sé de qué va. Pero dijo: "Nos asociaremos con Uds. pero no vamos a invertir en esto. Uds. necesitan encontrar una forma de traer esta campaña aquí y hacer que funcione". Así que lo que hicimos fue tomar parte del dinero que conseguimos en Australia para traer la campaña a este país, EE.UU., y al Reino Unido, e hicimos esto porque sabíamos, que si era un éxito, podríamos reunir infinitamente más dinero mundialmente del que podríamos reunir solo en Australia. Y ese dinero potenciaría la investigación que nos llevaría a una cura. Y no estamos en la búsqueda de una cura australiana o una cura canadiense, estamos buscando la cura. Así que en 2007, llevamos la campaña por aquí, y eso sentó las bases para la campaña. No fue tan exitosa como pensamos que sería. Estábamos muy entusiasmados con nuestro éxito en Australia y Nueva Zelanda en ese momento. Así que ese año realmente nos enseñó la importancia de ser pacientes y realmente entender el mercado local antes de ser muy vivos y poner metas elevadas. Pero me siento muy satisfecho de decir que en 2010 Movember se convirtió en un movimiento verdaderamente global. Canadá sola se adelantó en términos de ser la campaña de recaudación número uno del mundo. El año pasado tuvimos 450 000 Mo Bros repartidos por todo el mundo y juntos conseguimos 77 millones de dólares. (Aplausos) Y eso hace que Movember sea ahora la mayor fuente de financiación de investigación del cáncer de próstata y programas de apoyo en el mundo. Y eso es un logro increíble cuando se piensa en nosotros dejándonos el bigote. (Risas) Y para nosotros, ha redefinido la caridad. Nuestra cinta es una cinta peluda. (Risas) Nuestros embajadores son los Mo Bros y las Mo Sistas, y creo que han sido fundamentales para nuestro éxito. Llevamos nuestra marca y nuestra campaña a estas personas. Les dejamos adoptarlo e interpretarlo a su manera. Ahora vivo en Los Ángeles porque la Fundación de Cáncer de Próstata de los Estados Unidos tiene su sede allí y siempre me preguntan los medios de comunicación de allá, porque son muy orientados a las celebridades, "¿Quiénes son sus celebridades embajadoras?" Y les digo: "el año pasado tuvimos la suerte de tener 450 000 celebridades embajadoras". Y sueltan: "¿Qué, qué dice?" Y es que cada persona, cada uno de los Mo Bros y Mo Sistas que participan en Movember es nuestra celebridad embajadora, y es tan, tan importante y fundamental para nuestro éxito. Ahora quiero compartirles uno de mis más conmovedores momentos Movember, ocurrido aquí en Toronto el año pasado, al final de la campaña. Estaba con un equipo. Fue el final de Movember. Habíamos tenido una gran campaña, y para ser honesto, habíamos tenido nuestra dosis justa de cerveza esa noche, pero dije, "Saben qué, creo nos está faltando un bar". (Risas) Así que nos apilamos en un taxi, este es nuestro conductor, yo estaba sentado en el asiento trasero y él dio la vuelta y dijo: "¿A dónde van?" Y dije: "¡Espere! Ese es un bigote impresionante". (Risas) Y él dijo: "Lo estoy haciendo por Movember". Y dije: "Yo igual". Y dije: "Cuénteme su historia de Movember". Y dijo: "Mire, sé que es sobre la salud de los hombres, Sé que es sobre cáncer de próstata, pero esto es para el cáncer de mama". Y dije: "Bien, que interesante". Siguió: "El año pasado, mi mamá murió de cáncer de mama en Sri Lanka, porque no podíamos costear el tratamiento adecuado para ella", y dijo: "Este bigote es mi homenaje a mi mamá". Y estábamos todos conmovidos y en silencio atrás en el taxi y no le dije quien era, porque pensé que no era apropiado, y yo solo le estreché la mano y le dije: "Muchísimas gracias. Su mamá estaría tan orgullosa". Y desde ese momento me di cuenta de que Movember es mucho más que un bigote o hacer una broma. Se trata de cada persona que llega a estos programa, que lo adopta a su manera, y le da significado en su propia vida. Nosotros ahora en Movember, nos enfocamos en tres áreas del programa para tener un verdadero impacto: sensibilización y educación,
survivor support programs, and research. Now we always focus, naturally, on how much we raise, because it's a very tangible outcome, but for me, awareness and education is more important than the funds we raise, because I know that is changing and saving lives today, and it's probably best exampled by a young guy that I met at South by Southwest in Austin, Texas, at the start of the year. He came up to me and said, "Thank you for starting Movember." And I said, "Thank you for doing Movember." And I looked at him, and I was like, "I'm pretty sure you can't grow a mustache." (Laughter) And I said, "What's your Movember story?" And he said, "I grew the worst mustache ever." (Laughter) "But I went home for Thanksgiving dinner, and pretty quickly the conversation around the table turned to what the hell was going on." (Laughter) "And we talked -- I talked to them about Movember, and then after that, my dad came up to me, and at the age of 26, for the first time ever, I had a conversation with my dad one on one about men's health. I had a conversation with my dad about prostate cancer, and I learned that my grandfather had prostate cancer and I was able to share with my dad that he was twice as likely to get that disease, and he didn't know that, and he hadn't been getting screened for it." So now, that guy is getting screened for prostate cancer. So those conversations, getting men engaged in this, at whatever age, is so critically important, and in my view so much more important than the funds we raise. Now to the funds we raise, and research, and how we're redefining research. We fund prostate cancer foundations now in 13 countries. We literally fund hundreds if not thousands of institutions and researchers around the world, and when we looked at this more recently, we realized there's a real lack of collaboration going on even within institutions, let alone nationally, let alone globally, and this is not unique to prostate cancer. This is cancer research the world over. And so we said, right, we'd redefined charity. We need to redefine the way these guys operate. How do we do that? So what we did was, we created a global action plan, and we're taking 10 percent of what's raised in each country now and putting it into a global fund, and we've got the best prostate cancer scientific minds in the world that look after that fund, and they come together each year and identify the number one priority, and that, last year, was getting a better screening test. So they identified that as a priority, and then they've got and recruited now 300 researchers from around the world that are studying that topic, essentially the same topic. So now we're funding them to the tune of about five or six million dollars to collaborate and bringing them together, and that's a unique thing in the cancer world, and we know, through that collaboration, it will accelerate outcomes. And that's how we're redefining the research world. So, what I know about my Movember journey is that, with a really creative idea, with passion, with persistence, and a lot of patience, four mates, four mustaches, can inspire a room full of people, and that room full of people can go on and inspire a city, and that city is Melbourne, my home. And that city can go on and inspire a state, and that state can go on and inspire a nation, and beyond that, you can create a global movement that is changing the face of men's health. My name is Adam Garone, and that's my story. Thank you. (Applause)
programas de apoyo a sobrevivientes e investigación. Ahora bien, siempre nos concentramos en cuánto dinero recaudamos porque es un resultado tangible, pero para mí, la sensibilización y educación es más importante que los fondos que recaudamos, porque sé que es cambiar vidas, salvar vidas hoy, y probablemente el mejor ejemplo sea un joven que conocí en 'South by Southwest' en Austin, Texas, a principios de año. Se me acercó y dijo: "Gracias por comenzar Movember." Y dije: "Gracias por hacer Movember". Y lo miré diciendo: "Estoy seguro de que a Ud. no le crece el bigote". (Risas) Y dije: "¿Cuál es su historia de Movember?" Y dijo: "Tuve el peor bigote posible". (Risas) "Pero me fui a casa para la cena de Acción de Gracias y muy rápidamente la conversación alrededor de la mesa llevó a qué demonios estaba pasando". (Risas) "Y hablamos, hablé con ellos acerca de Movember, y después de eso, mi papá se me acercó, y a la edad de 26, por primera vez, tuve una conversación con mi papá uno a uno sobre la salud de los hombres. Tuve una conversación con mi papá sobre el cáncer de próstata y supe que mi abuelo tuvo cáncer de próstata y pude compartir con mi padre que él tiene el doble de posibilidades de tener la enfermedad y él lo sabía, y no se había hecho el examen". Así que ahora sí se hace el examen de cáncer de próstata. Así que esas conversaciones, que los hombres se comprometan con esto, a cualquier edad, es tan críticamente importante, en mi opinión mucho más importante que los fondos que recaudamos. Ahora sobre los fondos que recaudamos, la investigación y cómo estamos redefiniendo la investigación. Financiamos fundaciones de cáncer de próstata en 13 países. Financiamos literalmente cientos si no miles de instituciones e investigadores alrededor del mundo, y cuando miramos esto más recientemente, nos dimos cuenta de que hay una falta real de colaboración, incluso dentro de las instituciones, aún más a nivel nacional, aún más a nivel mundial, y esto no es exclusivo del cáncer de próstata. Esto pasa en toda la investigación de cáncer en el mundo. Por lo que hemos dicho, bien, hemos redefinido la caridad. Necesitamos redefinir la forma en que estas personas operan. ¿Cómo lo hacemos? Lo que hicimos fue crear un plan de acción mundial, y estamos tomando el 10 % de lo que se recauda en cada país, lo ponemos en un fondo global, y tenemos las mejores mentes científicas de cáncer de próstata en el mundo cuidando ese fondo, y se reúnen cada año e identifican la prioridad número uno, y, el año pasado, estaban tras una mejor prueba de detección. Por lo que lo identificaron como una prioridad y entonces han conseguido y reclutado a 300 investigadores de todo el mundo que están estudiando este tema, esencialmente el mismo tema. Así que ahora los estamos financiando con cinco o seis millones de dólares para colaborar y reunirlos, lo que es algo único en el cáncer mundial, y sabemos que, a través de esa colaboración, se acelerarán los resultados. Así es cómo estamos redefiniendo el mundo de la investigación. Por lo tanto, lo que sé sobre mi aventura de Movember es que, con una idea realmente creativa, con pasión, con persistencia y mucha paciencia, cuatro compañeros, cuatro bigotes, pueden inspirar una sala llena de gente, y esa sala llena de gente puede ir e inspirar a una ciudad, y esa ciudad es Melbourne, mi hogar. Y esa ciudad puede ir e inspirar a un estado y ese estado puede ir e inspirar una nación y más allá de eso, puede crear un movimiento global que cambie la cara de la salud de los hombres. Mi nombre es Adam Garone, y esa es mi historia. Gracias. (Aplausos)